<resources>

    <string name="app_name">inGenius</string>
    
    <string name="title_activity_main">inGenius</string>
    <string name="rulestext">1) It will be a 12 hour event that will consist of 10 hours dedicated for developing your hacks.
\n\n2) Each team must consist of at least 2 members and at most 3 members.
\n\n3) The total number of participants will be limited to 100. Hence, a first come first serve policy will be followed in the registration process. Please do note that registration will be done only if the team registers together.
\n\n4) The registration fee will be Rs.100 per person(Rs.200 for a team of 2 and Rs.300 for a team of 3)
\n\n5) The tickets are non refundable.
\n\n6) Food and refreshments will be provided on the day of the event.
\n\n7) Each team must get their own laptops and other hardware required to develop their hacks.
\n\n8) Access to power and wifi for all the participants will be ensured
\n\n9) Repository for software will be made available on the local network
\n\n10) You must bring a valid ID for verification purposes.
\n\n11) All your belongings are your sole responsibility. The organizer is not responsible for stolen / missing goods of any participant.
\n\n12) Hacks to be submitted have no domain restrictions and can be either hardware or software hacks or a combination of both
\n\n13) Teams may work on multiple hacks,but, can submit only one for reviewing to the judges.
\n\n14) You shall not submit any hack

    that is known by you to belong to someone else.
    that has already been worked on, either by you or by someone else; all hacks must be initiated and must end within the duration of the hackathon.
    that contains viruses, worms, spyware or other components or instructions that are malicious, deceptive, or designed to limit or harm the functionality of a computer.
    that violates third party copyrights, patents, trademarks, trade secrets or other proprietary rights or rights of publicity or privacy.
    that violates any law, statute, ordinance or regulation.
    that is, or may reasonably be considered to be, defamatory, libelous, hateful, racially or religiously biased or offensive, unlawfully threatening or unlawfully harassing to any individual, partnership or corporation.

\n\n15) You will not hold the organizer or the event sponsors liable for any content you submit for purposes of this competition.
\n\n16) We may, on notifying you, immediately suspend or terminate your rights, if you breach these rules or if we reasonably believe that you have submitted a contribution in violation of these rules.
\n\n17) The organizer reserves the right, in sole discretion, to suspend or cancel the contest at any time for any reason.
\n\n18) The jury reserves the right to go through the entire source code of your submitted hack and you guarantee that no part of it violates any aforementioned intellectual properties.
\n\n19) We may refuse your hack for any good reason.
\n\n20) The final winner will be decided based on the jury’s decision and organizer’s evaluation.
\n\n21) Organizer’s decision will be final and binding.</string>

</resources>